Morgan Russell
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Notes and Sketches, 1891-1977, Series 5:; (Reels 4528-4538)
  - Notebooks, undated (Reel 4537, Frame 819-1186)
  - Notebooks, undated (Reel 4538, Frame 1-730)
- Printed Material, 1908-1963, Series 6:; (Reels 4539-4541)
  This series contains a few exhibition announcements and catalogs, and also includes programs, printed travel souvenirs, music catalogs, clippings, book catalogs, calling cards, and miscellaneous printed material such as unused picture postcards. Music catalogs include a handwritten poem by Jean Cocteau.
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1909-1923 (Reel 4539, Frame 1-293)
  - Programs, 1908-1930 (Reel 4539, Frame 294-377)
  - Printed Travel Souvenirs, 1928-1934 (Reel 4539, Frame 378-462)
    Maps of Bologna, Milan, Naples, Rome and Provincia d'Novara
    Guide books
    Passenger list, 1932
    Souvenir menus, 1928-1932
    Tickets to Italian museums, 1933-1934
  - Music Catalogs, 1923-1939 (Reel 4539, Frame 463-711)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, 1921-1933 (Reel 4539, Frame 711-790)
    Campioni Dello Sport
    Vie D'Alexandre (in Latin)
    La Revue de L'Epoque magazine, 1921
    Les Cahiers De L'Artistes, 1931
    The Argus, 1927
    The California Artist, 1932
    Catalog of the Chouinard School of Art, 1932-1933
  - Clippings, 1908-1963 (Reel 4540, Frame 1-821)
  - Clippings, 1908-1963 (Reel 4541, Frame 1-44)
  - Clipping Fragments (Reel 4541, Frame 480-766)
  - Clipping Fragments (Reel 4541, Frame 783-988)
  - Book Catalogs, undated (Reel 4541, Frame 45-86)
  - Blank Picture Postcards of European Views of Works of Art (Reel 4541, Frame 87-401)
  - Calling Cards (Reel 4541, Frame 402-479)
    (Calling cards from: S. Aprile; Ben Zimra; W. J. Bernard; Jean Binion; Denyse Bouquillon; Albert Brunswig; Marguerite Carson; Mr. and Mrs. J. Gamble Cavallier; Mme. Jean Chapman; Mary Lou Couperot; Louis Courvoisier; Guthrie Dahl; Anton De Bersaques; Rene De Brot; Helene De Masi; Alexander De Noreuil; Mme. Lanthiez De Polignac; Princesse Edmond DeVegh; Helen Dracopoli; John Fontenelle; R. Francesconi; Emilie Gray; Richard Lemoyne Gray; Russell Merle Harper; R. G. Kirk; Alexander Landowski; Paul Lund; Andrew Boardo Matthews; Amory Miklosy; Ade Norregaard; Mogens Kai Patel; Jean Plechaty; Ladislav Poland; Reginald Rigal; Rene Sarfatti; Margherita G Stark; M. G. Tooby; Harold R. M. Traversari; Ester Danesi Uglietti; Enrico V. Usslar)
  - Notes (Reel 4541, Frame 767-782)
- Photographs, 1908-1948, Series 7:; (Reel 4542)
  Ths photographs found in this series are of Russell, his wife Suzanne, his friends, and his art work. Also included here is a 1917 photograph of Getrude Vanderbilt Whitney.
  - Photos of Morgan Russell, 1908-1938 (Reel 4542, Frame 1-24)
  - Photos of Morgan Russell, 1908-1938 (Reel 4542, Frame 83-93)
  - Photos of Morgan Russell, 1908-1938 (Reel 4542, Frame 168)
  - Photos of Morgan Russell, 1908-1938 (Reel 4542, Frame 174-175)
  - Photos of Morgan Russell, 1908-1938 (Reel 4542, Frame 205-207)
  - Photos of Morgan Russell, 1908-1938 (Reel 4542, Frame 293-294)
  - Photo of Gertrude Vanderbilt Whitney, 1917 (Reel 4542, Frame 135)
  - Photos of Wilma and Violet Brothers Shore, 1930 (Reel 4542, Frame 129-134)
  - Photos of Ruth Katz, one of Russell's Students (Reel 4542, Frame 155-162)
  - Photo of Vivi, undated (Reel 4542, Frame 169-170)
  - Photo of Walt Whitman, undated (Reel 4542, Frame 136)
  - Photo of Ms. Gentille Lucette Monde, March 3, 1948 (Reel 4542, Frame 163-166)
  - Photos of Works of Art (Reel 4542, Frame 25-82)
  - Photos of Works of Art (Reel 4542, Frame 94-128)
  - Photos of Works of Art (Reel 4542, Frame 137-162)
  - Photos of Works of Art (Reel 4542, Frame 167)
  - Photos of Works of Art (Reel 4542, Frame 171-173)
  - Photos of Works of Art (Reel 4542, Frame 176-204)
  - Photos of Works of Art (Reel 4542, Frame 208-292)
  - Photos of Works of Art (Reel 4542, Frame 295-318)
  - Photos of Works of Art, Portrait of Igor Stravinsky, Paris, Autumn 1915 (Reel 4542, Frame 291-292)